fccj.edu 2008-06-09

# student computing resources

 |  |  Activate Your Account  
---|---  
|  Change Student  
 Account Password  
|  Acceptable Use  
 Policy  
|  Privacy Policy  
|  Frequently Asked  
 Questions  
|  Google Apps  
|  Wireless Services   
|  Student Web Page  
 Hosting  
|  Student Web  
 Publishing  
 Instructions   
|  Student FrontPage  
 Resources   
|  Student PPP Dial-up  
| [ Learner Support  
 Center (Helpdesk)](http://www.distancelearning.org/learnersupport/index.html)  
|  Student Computing  
 Resources Home  
|  | 

| 

E-mail Privacy Policy  
  
---  
  
[Chapter 2006-232, Laws of Florida (PDF)](http://election.dos.state.fl.us/laws/06laws/ch_2006-232.pdf), requires Florida Community College to post the following notice:

Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to Florida Community College at Jacksonville. Instead, make contact by phone or in writing.  
  
College’s Internet Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Florida Community College at Jacksonville. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is not to collect personal information about you when you visit our Web site unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. 

When you visit our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our Web site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information. 

In addition, we gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our Web site by collecting information on the date, time and Web site pages accessed by visitors to the Web site. We do this so we can improve the content of our Web site and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected and individual visitors’ personal information is not identified. 

If you choose to share personal information with us — by sending us a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information — we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized or in support of College sponsored programs. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time to comply with Florida’s archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to other third parties or government agencies, unless required to do so by state or federal law or in support of university sponsored programs. 

If we are required to disclose information about you by law, we will make every effort to notify you of the disclosure in advance. 

If you have questions about our privacy policy, or have ideas about improving our policy, please e-mail the [Learner Support Center](mailto:helpdesk@fccj.edu), or you can reach us by telephone at 904.632.3151.

For information concerning privacy for students, faculty and staff, please see the College’s Acceptable Use Policy.
